question_data = [{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"American rapper Dr. Dre actually has a Ph.D. doctorate.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"The music group Daft Punk got their name from a negative review they received.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"The music video to The Buggle&#039;s &quot;Video Killed the Radio Star&quot; was the first music video to broadcast on MTV.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"Korean girl group, TWICE, consists of 9 members","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"Scatman John&#039;s real name was John Paul Larkin.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"Stevie Wonder&#039;s real name is Stevland Hardaway Morris.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"Michael Jackson wrote The Simpsons song &quot;Do the Bartman&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"Eurobeat is primarily an Italian genre of music.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"Daft Punk originated in France.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Music","question":"The song &quot;Stronger Than You&quot; is a single by Estelle, who played Garnet in Steven Universe.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]}]